contactfly.com 2014-02-19

# PRIVACY POLICY

PRIVACY POLICY

** PRIVACY POLICY**

This Privacy Policy governs your use of this Website and any content, products or services made available from or through this website including any sub domains thereof (“Website”).  We are committed to advising you of the right to your privacy and strive to provide a safe and secure user experience. This Privacy Policy sets forth the online data collection and usage policies and practices that apply to this web site. 

By using this site, you explicitly accept, without limitation or qualification, the collection, use and transfer of the personal information provided by you in the manner described in this Statement. Please read this Statement carefully as it affects your rights and liabilities under the law. If you disagree with the way we collect and process personal information, please do not use this website.

##  Scope of this Policy

This policy applies to this website and regulates the processing of information relating to you and grants both us and you various rights with respect to your personal data.  It describes what type of information we collect; how we use that information and to whom we can provide that information.  It also informs you of how to notify us to stop using your information. Our company is located in the United States.  You may be located in a country that has laws which are more restrictive about the collection and use of your personal information.  However, by using our site, you agree to waive the more restrictive laws and agree to be governed by the laws of the United States. 

This Site and emails received from us may also posts links to other web sites over which we have no control. As such, we are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of other web sites when you choose to link from this site. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those other web sites so you can understand how they collect, use and share your information. 

We also do not control the data use practices of those persons or entities who may access your information on this site for the purposes of providing the service or product you have requested or third party Ad Networks and other third parties with whom we work to serve you personalized ads on our site. We encourage you to review the privacy policies and opt-out choices of those third parties so you can understand how they collect, use and share your information.

##  Information We Collect and Retain

We collect the following general types of information about you when you visit and use our Site or through our emails: personal information, demographic information, behavioral information, and indirect information. Sometimes we collect combinations of these types of information.  

_ Personal information_ is information that can be used to identify you, or any other individual to whom the information may relate, personally. We do not collect personal information unless you choose to provide it to us. Some examples of personal information that we collect, depending on the services you use and local law, are: 

  * First and Last Name
  * Physical Address
  * Email address
  * Telephone number
  * Any other information you provide to us though the course of communicating with us. 

_ Demographic information_ is information that may or may not be unique to you in the sense that it refers to selected population characteristics, Such information may include, but is not limited to, zip code, telephone numbers (including cell phone numbers and carriers), birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, industry of employment, personal and online interests.

_ Behavioral information_ is information pertaining to how you use our site, the areas of our site that you visit, the emails that you open and link to the advertiser through what services you access, and information about your computer hardware and software including your IP address, geographic location, browser preference, operating system type, domain names, times that you access the internet and other website you have been referred to us through. This information is necessary for analyzing the use of resources, troubleshooting problems, preventing fraud, and improving our services and products. 

__ Third party information__ is information that we acquire from a third party which may include personal, demographic, behavioral and indirect information.  We obtain this information so that we can personalize the advertising to you shown our site or in our emails.   

__ Web Technology information__ is information we automatically collect from you when you open one of our emails or visit our site.  This includes information collected from the use of cookies, web beacons or java script. 

__No Information Collected from Children.__   Company will never knowingly collect any Personal Information about children under the age of 13.  If Company obtains actual knowledge that it has collected Personal Information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately deleted from its database.  Because it does not collect such information, Company has no such information to use or to disclose to third parties. 

##  Use of Cookies, Web Beacons, and Java Script

**__ Cookies:__** “Cookies” are a feature in your browser software. If enabled, we or a third party vendor may write cookies that may store small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to any of the pages of this Site or our emails. Cookies assist us in tracking which of our features appeal the most to you and what content you may have viewed on past visits. When you visit this site again, cookies can enable us to customize our content according to your preferences. We may use cookies to: keep track of the number of return visits to this site; accumulate and report aggregate, statistical information on website usage; deliver specific content to you based on your interests or past viewing history; save your password for ease of access to our Site.  You can disable cookies, although the Site may not function properly for you. Your browser preferences can be modified to accept or reject all cookies, or request a notification when a cookie is set. You may read more about cookies at [ http://cookiecentral.com](http://cookiecentral.com/). In order to use all of the features and functionality of Company’s websites, you need to accept cookies. 

We predominately use “session” cookies, which are not permanently stored on your hard drive. Session cookies expire after two hours of inactivity or when you close your browser. “Session” cookies allow us to keep track of this data until you have completed your search or registration. 

We may use “persistent” cookies primarily to ensure that we do not show you pages that you have already seen and to personalize your site experience and save you time. “Persistent” Cookies enable us to recognize whether you have responded to any questionnaire or registration or have already been presented with an advertisement or information placed on the site so that we do not show you the same information again the next time you visit our site or in the next email you receive from us. The “persistent” cookies we use will remain on your computer after you have left our site until you remove them.

We may also allow other companies to display advertisements to you while you are visiting our Sites and when opening our emails. Because your web browser must request these advertisements from the other companies’ servers, these companies can view, edit or set their own cookies, just as if you had requested a web page from their site. We have no control over the practices of those third party advertisers and are not responsible for their technology or tracking.  We encourage you to review the policies of such advertisers when you link to their website.

__ Removing Cookies:_  _You have the ability to accept, decline or move cookies at any time by modifying your browser settings. Please see [ http://cookiecentral.com](http://cookiecentral.com/). If you choose to decline cookies, however, that may hinder performance and negatively impact your experience on the web site.

You have the ability to limit our use of cookies. To opt-out of these cookies, please go to 

**__ Web Beacons__** ** _:_**    We also use electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs, clear gifs or action tags) that allow us to collect certain information about your visit to these Web pages (including the number of users who have visited those pages), measure and improve the effectiveness of advertisements, and deliver services. Web beacons are not used to access your personally identifiable information; they are a technique used to compile aggregated statistics about web site usage. Web beacons collect only a limited set of information including a cookie number, time and date of page view and a description of the page on which the Web beacon resides. This information may be shared with one or more third parties so that they can understand the kinds of visitors to the Web pages, how those visitors use those Web Pages, and the effectiveness of their advertisements. We may also use web beacons in email messages sent to individuals listed in our database.

__ Disabling Web Beacons._  _ Because Web beacons are the same as any other content request, you cannot opt out or refuse them. However, they can be rendered ineffective by either opting out of cookies or changing the cookie setup in your browser.

**__ JavaScript:__** ** __** We may also use JavaScript within certain advertisements. JavaScript is a computer language that enhances the functionality of websites, particularly in respect to pictures. We do not collecting any personal data via JavaScript but use it to analyze and improve the site’s functions. 

__ Disabling JavaScript:_  _You may deactivate JavaScript via your browser settings or activate it the same way. If you disable JavaScript you will not be able to use some of the functions of the website.

__IP Addresses.__  We automatically track certain information based upon your behavior on the site or from our emails. We may use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand, protect and serve you and our community. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on the site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on the site or not), your computer browser information, and your IP address. Your Internet Protocol ("IP") is a unique Internet "address" which is assigned to you by your Internet Service Provider ("ISP"). For local area network ("LAN"), DSL, or cable modem users, an IP address may be permanently assigned to a particular computer. IP addresses are automatically logged by Web servers, collecting information about a user's traffic patterns. While the IP address does not identify an individual by name, it may, with the cooperation of the ISP, be used to locate and identify an individual using the Web. Your IP address can, however, reveal what geographic area you are connecting from, or which ISP you are using. Finally, other websites you visit have IP addresses, and we may collect the IP addresses of those websites and their pages.

__Computer Profiles.__  Company may also collect and accumulate other anonymous data which will help us understand and analyze the Internet experience of our visitors. For instance, Company may accumulate visitor data relating to referring domain names, the type of browsers used, operating system software, screen resolutions, color capabilities, browser plug-ins, language settings, cookie preferences, search engine keywords and JavaScript enablement. When you provide us with Personal Identification Information, we are able to use such visitor data to identify you. 

##  How We Use the Information Collected 

__ Providing Services and Products.__  We use the information we gather for the purposes of providing the services and or products you have requested and to market third party products and services to you that may be of interest to you.  This may include passing your information on to a third party with which we have a contract to provide such services.  Although our contractual arrangement limits how such third party can use your information, we do not control the privacy practices of this third party.  If you have any questions or wish to remove your information from the third party’s database, you will need to contact that party directly. 

__ Improving our Website.__  We use the information we gather to respond to any inquires you make; operate and improve our Site or emails, improve and create a positive user experience with our site or emails;  and deliver the products and services advertised on our Site or in our emails.  Our services include the display of personalized products, content, and advertising relating to your experience and interests. The information we gather on this Site or through our emails may be shared with other companies under common ownership with ours throughout the world. 

##  Disclosure of Information to Others

We disclose to third parties throughout the world your personal information, combined personal, demographic, behavioral or indirect information, as set forth below: 

__ Product and Service Delivery._   _ We may share your information with third parties who delivery the products and services you have requested. We disclose information to companies and individuals we employ to perform technical functions on our behalf. Examples include third parties who host our website, analyze our data, provide marketing assistance, and provide customer service. 

__ Third Party Products and Services__. We may disclose such information to third parties to provide you with information about the opportunities, products or services of third parties.  We use the data and data logs we have about you, including interests and preferences you have expressed, to determine whether you might be interested in the opportunities, products or services of a particular third party. This type of marketing may be in the form of email offers or mobile offers sent to you by third parties or telemarketing calls from third parties. 

__ Anonymous information_.  _We also share aggregated anonymous information about you and other persons using our Site or opening our emails with third parties so that they can understand the kinds of visitors to the Site and how those visitors use the Sites.  This includes demographic information and behavioral information.

__ Legal Process__. We disclose information if legally required to do so, or at our discretion pursuant to a request from a governmental entity or if we believe in good faith – after considering your privacy interests and other factors – that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; (b) protect our rights or property or our affiliated companies; (c) prevent a crime or protect national security; or (d) protect the personal safety of users or the public. 

__ Acquisition or Merger__. We may disclose and transfer information to a third party who acquires any or all of our business, whether such acquisition is by way of merger, consolidation or purchase of all or a substantial portion of our assets. In addition, in the event we become the subject of an insolvency proceeding, whether voluntary or involuntary, we or our liquidator, administrator, receiver or administrative receiver may sell, license or otherwise dispose of such information in a transaction approved by the court. You will be notified of the sale of all or a substantial portion of our business to a third party by email or through a prominent notice posted on the Site.

Again, in each of these situations, the recipients of your data may potentially be located in any country in the world. 

##   

##  Third Party Use of Your Information

##  Third parties also collect and use information about you on our Site in the following way:

## __  Advertiser cookies and web beacons.__ Advertising agencies, advertising networks, and other companies who place advertisements on the Site or in our emails and on the internet generally may use their own cookies, web beacons, and other technology to collect information about you. We do not control the use of such technology and have no responsibility for the use of such technology to gather information about you. 

## __ Hyperlinks__.  Our Site and email messages sometimes contain hypertext links to the websites of third parties. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites. Such links are provided for your convenience and reference only. We do not operate or control in any respect any information, software, products or services available on such third party websites. The inclusion of a link to a website does not imply any endorsement of the services or the site, its contents, or its sponsoring organization. 

##  Use of Your Information for Email and Telemarketing

## __ Email and Unsubscribe Policy.__  We may provide your personal information to third parties for promotional offers by email.  These offers may be our services and products or those of third parties.  We may maintain separate email lists for different purposes.  If email recipients wish to end their email subscription from a particular list, they need to follow the instructions at the end of each email message to unsubscribe from the particular list.  To unsubscribe from all Company’s email lists, a person must send an email to unsubscribe: [ Unsubscribe@ContactFly.com](mailto:Unsubscribe@ContactFly.com)

## __ Content of Email Messages.__  You may receive certain commercial email messages sent by third parties for products which may be of interest to you.  In such case, an Advertiser's name will appear in the "From:" and the email will have a method at the bottom of the email to unsubscribe from that Advertiser.   Company is not responsible for third party emails sent to you.

## __ Opting Out of Email Marketing Material.__ We provide you the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when it asks for this information. For example, if you purchase a product/service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference by emailing or calling us per the information contained on our contact page.

##  If you no longer wish to receive our promotions, you may opt-out of receiving it by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us per the information contained on our contact page. 

##  Customer Care Contact Information: [ CONTACT@ContactFly.com](mailto:CONTACT@ContactFly.com) ; 

## __ Telemarketing.__  We  may use your Personal Information to advertise, directly or indirectly, to individuals using direct mail marketing or telemarketing using telephones and cell phones. You may have your telephone number or cell phone number listed on a state or federal do not call registry.  By registering and using this Site, you agree that such act constitutes a purchase, an inquiry and/or an application for purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule, 16 CFR §310 et seq. (the "ATSR"). Notwithstanding that your telephone number may be listed on the Federal Trade Commission's Do-Not-Call List, you have authorized us to contact you via telemarketing in accordance with the ATSR.  Moreover, by registering with, or requesting information from, a third-party advertiser at or through the Website or other advertisement media made available by us (e.g., email marketing), you agree that such action shall constitute a purchase, an inquiry and/or an application with the respective third-party advertiser for purposes of the ATSR and you may be contacted via email, direct mail and/or telemarketing by such third-party advertiser in accordance with the ATSR. We may use Personal Information to provide the services you've requested, including services that display customized content and advertising. 

## __ Wireless Addresses.__  If the e-mail address you provide to us is a wireless e-mail address, you agree to receive messages at such address from us or our business associates (unless and until you have elected not to receive such messages by following the instructions in the unsubscribe portion of this policy).  You understand that your wireless carrier's standard rates apply to these messages.  You represent that you are the owner or authorized user of the wireless device on which messages will be received, and that you are authorized to approve the applicable charges.

## __ Short Message Service__.  We may make available a service through which you can receive messages on your wireless device via short message service (“SMS Service”).  Data obtained from you in connection with this SMS service may include your name, address, cell phone number, your provider's name, and the date, time, and content of your messages. You represent that you are 18 years of age and the owner or authorized user of the wireless device on which messages will be received, and that you are authorized to approve the applicable charges.  In addition to any fee of which you are notified your provider's standard messaging rates apply to our confirmation and all subsequent SMS correspondence.  All charges are billed by and payable to your mobile service provider. We will not be liable for any delays in the receipt of any SMS messages, as delivery is subject to effective transmission from your network operator. SMS message services are provided on an AS IS basis.  We may also obtain the date, time and content of your messages in the course of your use of the SMS Service.  We will use the information we obtain in connection with our SMS Service in accordance with this Privacy Policy.  If fees are charged to your wireless account invoice, we may provide your carrier with your applicable information in connection therewith.  Your wireless carrier and other service providers may also collect data about your wireless device usage, and their practices are governed by their own policies.

##  You acknowledge and agree that the SMS Service is provided via wireless systems which use radios (and other means) to transmit communications over complex networks.  We do not guarantee that your use of the SMS Service will be private or secure, and we are not liable to you for any lack of privacy or security you may experience.  You are fully responsible for taking precautions and providing security measures best suited for your situation and intended use of the SMS Service.  We may also access the content of your account and wireless account with your carrier for the purpose of identifying and resolving technical problems and service-related complaints. 

## __ Removal of Wireless or SMS addresses:__ You may remove your information from our database. If you remove your information from our database it will no longer be used by Company for secondary purposes, disclosed to third parties, or used by Company or third parties to send promotional correspondence to you. You may remove your information by sending your request in writing via email to [ unsubscribe@ContactFly.com](mailto:unsubscribe@ContactFly.com). 

** Security**

##  We endeavor to safeguard and protect your information. When you submit information at the website, such information is protected both online and offline. The servers in which we store Personal Information are kept in a secure physical environment. We have security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of personal information under our control. Currently, We use Secure Socket Layer Software ("SSL") to protect data and to secure any transactions. SSL encrypts information, including credit card numbers, names and addresses as they are transmitted over the Internet. Please be advised that, although We take commercially reasonable technological precautions to protect your data, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, We cannot and do not warrant that your information will be absolutely secure. Any transmission of data at or through this site is at your own risk. However, access to your information is strictly limited, and not accessible to the public.

##  Changes to Privacy Statement

We reserve the right to make material changes to the substance of this Privacy Statement.  We will post those changes through a prominent notice on the web site so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and to whom we will disclose it.

##  Your California Rights

A California resident who has provided personal information to a business with whom he/she has established a business relationship for personal, family, or household purposes (“California customer”) is entitled to request information about whether the business has disclosed personal information to any third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. In general, if the business has made such a disclosure of personal information, upon receipt of a request by a California customer, the business is required to provide a list of all third parties to whom personal information was disclosed in the preceding calendar year, as well as a list of the categories of personal information that were disclosed.

However, under the law, a business is not required to provide the above-described lists if the business adopts and discloses to the public (in its privacy policy) a policy of not disclosing customer’s personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless the customer first affirmatively agrees to the disclosure, as long as the business maintains and discloses this policy. Rather, the business may comply with the law by notifying the customer of his or her right to prevent disclosure of personal information and providing a cost free means to exercise that right.

As stated in this policy, you have agreed to allow us to share information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes until you remove your information and thus, agreement for such disclosure. To prevent disclosure of your personal information for use in direct marketing by a third party, do not opt in to such use when you provide personally identifiable information on one of our sites or contact us via email to remove your information from our database. Please note that whenever you opt in to receive future communications from a third party, your information will be subject to the third party's privacy policy. If you later decide that you do not want that third party to use your information, you will need to contact the third party directly, as we have no control over how third parties use information. You should always review the privacy policy of any party that collects your information to determine how that entity will handle your information.

California customers may request further information about our compliance with this law by e-mailing [ CONTACT@ContactFly.com](mailto:CONTACT@ContactFly.com). Please note that we are only required to respond to one request per customer each year, and we are not required to respond to requests made by means other than through this e-mail address.
